You know. I love artificial intelligence. I
think it's great. It's going to be super
intelligent. It's going to really be
fantastic. But right now. I really love it as
a tool.
like a hammer. And right now. people are using
it as hammers in the real estate space. And
this is
probably the only video I'm going to do about
this. just for the simple fact that real
estate
agents might want to learn a little earlier
than the rest of the world's going to find
out. And
that is. if you're making content to try to
become famous. like dancing cats or pirates or
aliens or
AI systems doing horrible things. That's fine.
But when you start to clone yourself as a real
estate agent. you look lazy. You look like you
don't have the time to actually take care and
educate and give more of yourself for your
clients and not even the clients you have.
Once you have them and they start dealing with
you. who knows? Maybe they like you. Maybe
they think that you're the best thing since
sliced bread. So in those spaces. trying to
send them
some kind of a virtual video that you had one
of these avatar systems make.
that's going to be a non-starter as well.
You'll be dealing with them on the human
level.
But now we have these major real estate brands
going out and they're using avatar tools
and they're having them create their AI
avatar. And this isn't complicated. Anybody
can do it.
And then they're having them produce content.
So instead of the time needing to be taken by
the human agent. Now. basically. the script is
written by AI. The AI is given over. The AI
gives
the script to agent. It's really a hands-off
process all the way through. The video is
created.
The video gets syndicated. gets cut up into
pieces. B-rolls are added. the whole nine
yards. Then it
gets sent out to wherever the agent wants it
to be sent. I believe in time that's going to
devalue
a real estate agent. So if you're thinking
about doing this. I would probably say if you
haven't
done videos yet. you're looking at this as
being your edge. It might get you more places
than not
doing videos at all. or is getting you. but it
really is something to consider because people
are going to start thinking. not only do they
not like seeing you with your fancy car. your
fancy
jet. or whatever fancy things that you have.
that really does. it's not appreciated by a
majority of
the people out there. You're not that kind of
an influencer. I mean. maybe the people at the
top
building out the tech and doing all these
other things. maybe people like to celebrate
their
success. But real estate agents. you're a
service provider. you should be there to
protect your
client. protect their interest in the real
estate transaction. and watch out for them and
advise
them and things that they can't see coming and
you don't know or might want to try to expect
so
they can head off the problem at the pass. So
if you're going to start doing videos and
you're
going to start parsing those videos out to AI
to be able to be completed and finished for
you.
finishing is fine. But as long as you're the
one acting it out. you're the one talking.
you're the one speaking you can use AI to do
it all sorts of fancy cuts and cutaways and
all this other stuff but you really i think
need to be in that game and i'm probably not
going to do this
because when i see agents doing these things
that aren't really they themselves i'm i'm
happy because
that doesn't hurt me it helps i'm connor with
honor we'll see you tomorrow